Resume

Personal details

Name Nika Nishnianidze

Email address nika.nishnianidze.10@gmail.com

Phone number +995 571087098

Address Gldani, 4 M/D, 0167 Tbilisi

Date of birth April 20, 1998

Gender Male

Website yolosopher.online



Profile

Hello! I'm Nika Nishnianidze, a seasoned JavaScript Developer with three years of experience in both frontend and back-end development, specializing in the MERN and PERN stacks. I excel in crafting sleek interfaces using SASS/SCSS, Tailwind CSS, and Styled-Components, and ensuring smooth functionality with Redux, Zustand, and useContext. Excited to apply my expertise and collaborate on meaningful projects

Education

Sep 2018 - Jun 2020 Business Management

Ilia State University, Tbilisi

Sep 2016 - May 2018 Philosophy

Ilia State University, Tbilisi

After studying philosophy for two years, I developed an interest in

economics and switched faculties.

Employment

Sep 2021 - Dec 2023 Frontend Developer

Lime Consulting, Ukraine, Kyiv (Remote)

This job was also a fantastic experience where I tackled new challenges,

working on the frontend of various gambling websites.

Apr 2020 - Aug 2021 Frontend Developer

Smartweb, Tbilisi

My first job was a great learning experience where I worked on various

projects and gained a lot of hands-on experience in frontend

development.

Certificates

Feb 2020 Smart Academy - Front-End Development Course

A(90 + out of 100)

Nov 2021 Smart Academy - ReactJS Course

A(90 + out of 100)

Moderate

Skills

Git/Github/Gitlab Excellent

HTML5, CSS/SASS Excellent

Typescript/Javascript/JQuery Excellent

API/CRUD Excellent

SocketIO/Websockets Excellent

MongoDB/Mongoose/Firebase Excellent

NodeJS/ExpressJS/NestJS Very good

ReactJS/NextJS Very good

Webpack/Gulp/Vite Very good

PostgreSQL/MySQL Good

,

Compose/Deployment

Languages

Docker/Docker

Georgian Fluent

English Very good

Qualities

- Deepthinker(in a good way)
- Quick learner, Smart
- Exemplary sense of accountability
- Good sense of humor, Cheerful, Team worker
- Determined and Goal-oriented
- Composed and Self-assured